Finding Aid for Topographic Quadrangle Maps, 1895-[ongoing].
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 7.5 Minute, Scale 1:24,000
  - Palmer- Shereman City
    - St. Ignace 45084G6 (Folder St. Ignace-Sanford)
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - St. Jacques 45086H6
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - St. Johns North 43084A5
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
    - St. Johns South 42084H5
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1973; photorevised
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - St. Louis 43084D5
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - St. Martin Island 45084H5
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Salem 42083D5
      - Survey 1942; print 1945, green overprint
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Saline 42083B7
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Sand Lake 43085C5
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Sand Lake SW 43085C6
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Sand Point 43083H4
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Sand River 46087D1
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Sands 46087D4
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Sandusky 43082D7
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Sanford 43084F4
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Saranac 42085H2 (Folder Saranac-Sherman City)
      - Survey 1975; print 1978; reprint 1979, green overprint
    - Saubee Lake 42085F1
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Saugatuck 42086F2
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Sault Ste. Marie South 46084D3
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Saunders Creek 45084A4
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Schaffer 45087G3
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Schoolcraft 42085A6
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1979; photorevised, green overprint
    - Schoolcraft NW 42085B6
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Seagull Point 45087E3
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Sebewaing 43083F4
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Secord Lake 44084A3
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Selkirk 44084C1
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Seney 46085C8
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Seney NW 46085D8
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Seul Choix Point 45085H8
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Shabbona 43083E1
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Shaftsburg 42084G3
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Shallows 46084D4
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1954; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Sharon 44085E1
      - Survey 1983; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Sheephead Lake 46085F2
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
    - Shelldrake 46085F1
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Shepherd 43084E6
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Sheridan 43085B1
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Sherman City 43085F1
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
  - Shields - Yuma
    - Shields 43084D1 (Folder Shields-Sodus)
      - Survey 1975; print 1975; reprint 1978, green overprint
    - Shiloh 43085A1
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Shot Point 46087E1
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Sid Town 44083D5
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Sidnaw 46088E6
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Sigma 44085F1
      - Survey 1984; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Silver Lake 45084B3
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Silver Lake Basin 46087F7
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Sister Lakes 42086A2
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Six Lakes 43085D2
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Skandia 46087D2
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Skanee North 46088H2
      - Survey 1982; print 1984; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Skanee South 46088G2
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Skeels 44084A5
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Skidway Lake 44084B1
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Smith Lake 46086A2
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Smiths Creek 42082H5
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1989; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Smithville 44085E2
      - Survey 1983; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Smoky Lake 46088A8
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1981, green overprint
      - Survey 1981; print 1981; reprint 1990, green overprint
    - Smyrna 43085A3
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Snover 43082D8
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Sodus 42086A3
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Somerset Center 42084A4 (Folder Somerset Center-Starvation Lake)
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Soo Junction 46085C3
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - South Boardman 44085F3
      - Survey 1983; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - South Branch 44083D8
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - South Fox Island 45085D7
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - South Lyon 42083D6
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - South Point 44083H3
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - South Range 47088A6
      - Survey 1946; print 1948, green overprint
      - Survey 1946; print 1946; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Southeast Albion 42084B6
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Southwest Albion 42084B7
      - Survey 1976; print 1980; reprint 1980, green overprint
    - Sparr 45084A5
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Sparta 43085B6
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1972; photorevised, green overprint
    - Spencer Lake 44083C3
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Spring Arbor 42084B5
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Springport 42084D6
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Sprinkler Lake 44083E5
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Spruce 44083G4
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Stager 45088H3
      - Survey 1945; print 1947
        [later edition titled Florence West]
    - Stalwart 46084A2
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Standish 43083H8
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Standish NE 43083H7
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969, green overprint
    - Stanton 43085C1
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1982; photorevised, green overprint
    - Stanwood 43085E4
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Star Corners 44086B2
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - Starvation Lake 44084G8
      - Survey 1983; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Sterling 44084A1 (Folder Sterling-Tecumseh South)
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Sterling NW 44084B2
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Sterling SW 44084A2
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Stevensville 42086A5
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Stewart Lake 44085A7
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - Stony Point 41083H3
      - Survey 1940; print 1942
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1953, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1978; photorevised, green overprint
    - Strongs 46084C8
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Sturgis 41085G4
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1962, green overprint
    - Sugar Mountain 47089H1
      - Survey 1984; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Sullivan 43086B1
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Sullivan Creek 46084C7
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Summit Lake 46088F1
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Sumner 43084C7
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Sumnerville 41086H2
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Sunken Lake 46086D1
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Sunset Lake 46088B5
      - Survey 1945; print 1945, green overprint
      - Survey 1945; print 1945; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Swartz Creek 42083H7
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Swimming Hole Creek 46087A3
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Sylvania 41083F6
      - Survey 1951; print 1952; reprint 1980, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Tahquamenon Lakes 46085D7
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Tallman 43086H1
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - Tawas City 44083C5
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Tecumseh North 42083A8
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969, green overprint
    - Tecumseh South 41083H8
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Tekonsha 42084A8 (Folder Tekonsha-Traverse Island)
      - Survey 1976; print 1980; reprint 1980, green overprint
    - Tenderfoot Lake 46089B5
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Thompsons Harbor 45083C5
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Thornville 42083H2
      - Survey 1943; print 1945
      - Survey 1943; print 1945, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Thousand Island Lake 46089B4
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Three Lakes 46088E2
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Three Oaks 41086G5
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Three Rivers East 41085H5
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Three Rivers West 41085H6
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1974, green overprint
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1979; photorevised, green overprint
    - Thumb Lake 45084B7
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Thunder Bay Island 45083A2
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Tie Lake 46086B6
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Tift Corner 43085D5
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Timberlost 46085E2
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Tipler 45088H6
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Tipton 42084A1
      - Survey 1976; print 1980; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Todd Harbor 48088A7
      - Survey 1984; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Toledo 41083F5
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1968, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Tower 45084C3
      - Survey 1982; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Townsend Lake 43085H8
      - Survey 1982; print 1987; reprint 1987, green overprint
    - Traverse Island 47088A3
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Trenary 46086B8 (Folder Trenary-Wacousta)
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Triangle Ranch 46088C4
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Trout Lake 46085B1
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Trufant 43085C3
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Tunis 46088D5
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Turtle Lake 44084H5
      - Survey 1950; print 1951
      - Survey 1950; print 1950; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Twin Lake 43086C2
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Ubly 43082F8
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Udell 44086B1
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - Utica 42083F1
      - Survey 1944; print 1946
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Vanderbilt 45084B6
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Vassar 43083C5
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Vega 45087G5
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Vermilac 46088E4
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Vermilion 46085G2
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
    - Vermilion SE 46085G1
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
    - Vestaburg 43084D8
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Vicksburg 42085A5
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Vulcan 45087G7
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
    - Waco Lake 46086A6
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Wacousta 42084G6
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1973; photorevised
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
    - Wagarville 44084A4 (Folder Wagarville-Warren)
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Wakefield 46089D8
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Wakefield NE 46089D7
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Wakeley Lake 44084F5
      - Survey 1950; print 1951
    - Waldenburg 42082F8
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Walkerville East 43086F1
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Walkerville West 43086F2
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Walkup Lake 43085F8
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Walled Lake 42083E4
      - Survey 1942; print 1945
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Walsh 46086C2
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Walton 44085E4
      - Survey 1983; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Warren 42083E1
      - Survey 1944; print 1946
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1953, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Waucedah 45087G6 (Folder Waucedah-Winn)
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Wayne 42083C4
      - Survey 1941; print 1943, green overprint
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Wayne County Airport 42083B3
      - Survey 1940; print 1942
    - Weidman 43084F8
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Wellston 44085B8
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - Wellston NE 44085B7
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - West Branch 44084C2
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - West Highland 42083F6
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Westwood 44085G1
      - Survey 1983; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Wheatland 41084H4
      - Survey 1962; print 1962; reprint 1963, green overprint
    - Whipple Lake 43085G6
      - Survey 1982; print 1987; reprint 1987, green overprint
    - White Cloud 43085E7
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - White Pine 46089G5
      - Survey 1948; print 1949
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Whitefish Point 46084F8
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
    - Whitney 45087G4
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Whitney Bay 45083H7
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Whittemore 44083B7
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Wildwood 45084C6
      - Survey 1982; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Willard 43084F1
      - Survey 1962; print 1962; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1962; print 1962; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Williamston 42084F3
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Wilson 45087F4
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Windigo 47089H2
      - Survey 1984; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Winn 43084E8
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Witch Lake 46088C1 (Folder Witch Lake-Yuma)
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Witch Lake NE 46088D1
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1956, green overprint
    - Wixom 42083E5
      - Survey 1942; print 1945
        [later editions titled Milford]
    - Wolf Lake 43086C1
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Wolverine 45084C5
      - Survey 1982; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Wood Island 46086E6
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Wood Island SE 46086E5
      - Survey 1981; print 1984; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Woodbury 42085G1
      - Survey 1975; print 1978; reprint 1979, green overprint
    - Wooden Shoe Village 43084H3
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Woodland 42085F2
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Woodland Park 43085F7
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Woodlawn 45087H3
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Woodville 43085F6
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Woodville NE 43085F5
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Wyandotte 42083B2
      - Survey 1940; print 1942
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1981; photorevised, green overprint
    - Yale 43082B7
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1963, green overprint
    - Ypsilanti East 42083B5
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Ypsilanti West 42083B6
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Yuma 44085C7